[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "Why aren't you as a productive two superstars just lying on some sun lounger in a bikini spending daddy's money being a brat?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "n't", "you", "as", "a", "productive", "two", "superstars", "just", "lying", "on", "some", "sun", "lounger", "in", "a", "bikini", "spending", "daddy", "'s", "money", "being", "a", "brat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "That's a really good question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "really", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "Where do you get this desire to scare people?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "get", "this", "desire", "to", "scare", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "Well, you know, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "When you were trying to analyze the best way to do it -- you're one of the best people to ask -- what is it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "were", "trying", "to", "analyze", "the", "best", "way", "to", "do", "it", "--", "you", "'re", "one", "of", "the", "best", "people", "to", "ask", "--", "what", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Well, first of all, you have to have really good characters because if you don't have somebody that you really want to spend time with, it might be -- it's going to be a workman like sort of book.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "you", "have", "to", "have", "really", "good", "characters", "because", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "have", "somebody", "that", "you", "really", "want", "to", "spend", "time", "with", ",", "it", "might", "be", "--", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "a", "workman", "like", "sort", "of", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "What conclusions did you draw after that about the death penalty?", "question_tokens": ["What", "conclusions", "did", "you", "draw", "after", "that", "about", "the", "death", "penalty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "I was very disturbed.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "very", "disturbed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Is that how you feel?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "how", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "ORNWELL: I do.", "answer_tokens": ["ORNWELL", ":", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "Where do you draw the line as a writer?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "draw", "the", "line", "as", "a", "writer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "I draw the line like I was saying a minute ago, like if someone said, do you want to watch an execution for research purposes, I would say no.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "draw", "the", "line", "like", "I", "was", "saying", "a", "minute", "ago", ",", "like", "if", "someone", "said", ",", "do", "you", "want", "to", "watch", "an", "execution", "for", "research", "purposes", ",", "I", "would", "say", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "How do you feel about the people that rejected you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "the", "people", "that", "rejected", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Well, the first three books I wrote they should have rejected, they were really awful.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "first", "three", "books", "I", "wrote", "they", "should", "have", "rejected", ",", "they", "were", "really", "awful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "And are you a Democrat?", "question_tokens": ["And", "are", "you", "a", "Democrat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "I think I am a Democrat now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "am", "a", "Democrat", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Is President Obama that person?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "President", "Obama", "that", "person", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "WDT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "I think we should give him another chance.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "we", "should", "give", "him", "another", "chance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "If you're a crime writer of your renown, do you read that kind of thing in the paper and get, you know, pretty excited?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "'re", "a", "crime", "writer", "of", "your", "renown", ",", "do", "you", "read", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", "in", "the", "paper", "and", "get", ",", "you", "know", ",", "pretty", "excited", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "I've not only heard about that, I went -- looked at the autopsy report.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "not", "only", "heard", "about", "that", ",", "I", "went", "--", "looked", "at", "the", "autopsy", "report", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "Did you really?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "And what was your conclusion?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "was", "your", "conclusion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "That it was a really well done autopsy and there is no evidence whatsoever that she was a victim of foul play.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "it", "was", "a", "really", "well", "done", "autopsy", "and", "there", "is", "no", "evidence", "whatsoever", "that", "she", "was", "a", "victim", "of", "foul", "play", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "Do you have crazies coming after you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "crazies", "coming", "after", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "Sure, you get some.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", ",", "you", "get", "some", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "Is this true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "She's attached to it and we're hoping to begin filming next year.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "attached", "to", "it", "and", "we", "'re", "hoping", "to", "begin", "filming", "next", "year", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "How cool is that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "cool", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "I think it's going to be way cool, lots of fun.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "way", "cool", ",", "lots", "of", "fun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "That's what you want to hear, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "you", "want", "to", "hear", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Do you ever do that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "I think about it every day, because I still get inspiration from cases I had back then, clients I knew, people I knew back 20, 30 years ago.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "about", "it", "every", "day", ",", "because", "I", "still", "get", "inspiration", "from", "cases", "I", "had", "back", "then", ",", "clients", "I", "knew", ",", "people", "I", "knew", "back", "20", ",", "30", "years", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Was there a wakeup moment, a utopia moment when you went, whoa?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "there", "a", "wakeup", "moment", ",", "a", "utopia", "moment", "when", "you", "went", ",", "whoa", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "No, it was very gradual.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "was", "very", "gradual", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitch"]}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 297, "question": "CDEERE: Reveal privileged information that violates attorney- client confidences, get me disbarred then testify in open court against the mafia?", "question_tokens": ["CDEERE", ":", "Reveal", "privileged", "information", "that", "violates", "attorney-", "client", "confidences", ",", "get", "me", "disbarred", "then", "testify", "in", "open", "court", "against", "the", "mafia", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "-NONE-", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "Well, unfortunately, Mitch --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "unfortunately", ",", "Mitch", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "But that's not true in real life, is it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "that", "'s", "not", "true", "in", "real", "life", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "It's certainly not true in real life.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "certainly", "not", "true", "in", "real", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "EX", "MD", "VB", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "What do you make of that debate, given the way that the law has changed due to technology in many ways?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "that", "debate", ",", "given", "the", "way", "that", "the", "law", "has", "changed", "due", "to", "technology", "in", "many", "ways", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Well, if not for DNA, there would be no Innocence Project.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "not", "for", "DNA", ",", "there", "would", "be", "no", "Innocence", "Project", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Do you think it's time just to move on?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "time", "just", "to", "move", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Well, personally, yes, I'm opposed to the death penalty, very much opposed to it for a lot of reasons, moral reasons but also questions of fairness, how it's implemented.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "personally", ",", "yes", ",", "I", "'m", "opposed", "to", "the", "death", "penalty", ",", "very", "much", "opposed", "to", "it", "for", "a", "lot", "of", "reasons", ",", "moral", "reasons", "but", "also", "questions", "of", "fairness", ",", "how", "it", "'s", "implemented", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "What did you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Didn't really follow that closely.", "answer_tokens": ["Did", "n't", "really", "follow", "that", "closely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "Do you think the right verdict was reached in that case?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "the", "right", "verdict", "was", "reached", "in", "that", "case", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "You know, I hate to pass judgment.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "hate", "to", "pass", "judgment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "The Muppets, Miss Piggy, dream come true?", "question_tokens": ["The", "Muppets", ",", "Miss", "Piggy", ",", "dream", "come", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNPS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Dream come true.", "answer_tokens": ["Dream", "come", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Miss Piggy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Because how is it going to get any better than this?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "how", "is", "it", "going", "to", "get", "any", "better", "than", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Let's have a little look at this, because this is the stuff of dreams.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "have", "a", "little", "look", "at", "this", ",", "because", "this", "is", "the", "stuff", "of", "dreams", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "Did you fund a celebrity?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "fund", "a", "celebrity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Yeah, I wanted to talk to you about that.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "wanted", "to", "talk", "to", "you", "about", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "How could do you that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "could", "do", "you", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "Best acting I've ever done in my life.", "answer_tokens": ["Best", "acting", "I", "'ve", "ever", "done", "in", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Why aren't you, as a productive of two superstars, just lying on some sun lounger in a bikini, spending daddy's money, being a brat?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "n't", "you", ",", "as", "a", "productive", "of", "two", "superstars", ",", "just", "lying", "on", "some", "sun", "lounger", "in", "a", "bikini", ",", "spending", "daddy", "'s", "money", ",", "being", "a", "brat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "That's a really good question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "really", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson", "Ray Charles"]}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Biggest names that walked through that door?", "question_tokens": ["Biggest", "names", "that", "walked", "through", "that", "door", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "Michael Jackson, Ray Charles.", "answer_tokens": ["Michael", "Jackson", ",", "Ray", "Charles", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Didn't you go in a car with Michael Jackson once and spray gun complete strangers with a water pistol?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "n't", "you", "go", "in", "a", "car", "with", "Michael", "Jackson", "once", "and", "spray", "gun", "complete", "strangers", "with", "a", "water", "pistol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "CC", "VB", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "It was a childish prank, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "childish", "prank", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "You actually did that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "actually", "did", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "That guy just knew how to do it, didn't he?", "question_tokens": ["That", "guy", "just", "knew", "how", "to", "do", "it", ",", "did", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "He did.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "That would have been that, right?", "question_tokens": ["That", "would", "have", "been", "that", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Maybe I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "But did you have any kind of gut feeling you wanted to be like them, be a star?", "question_tokens": ["But", "did", "you", "have", "any", "kind", "of", "gut", "feeling", "you", "wanted", "to", "be", "like", "them", ",", "be", "a", "star", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "Well, you know, the star part of it was never interesting to me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "star", "part", "of", "it", "was", "never", "interesting", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "That is so sweet, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "is", "so", "sweet", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "So sweet.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "sweet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "What does he think your biggest talent is?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "he", "think", "your", "biggest", "talent", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "That's funny.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "funny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "Home run, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Home", "run", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "You want to come touch the turtle?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "to", "come", "touch", "the", "turtle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "And nourishing the soul.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "nourishing", "the", "soul", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "Hey, did you maybe tell people that I diagnosed that guy with mumps based on his porn photo?", "question_tokens": ["Hey", ",", "did", "you", "maybe", "tell", "people", "that", "I", "diagnosed", "that", "guy", "with", "mumps", "based", "on", "his", "porn", "photo", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 638, "question": "What's going on?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "Um --", "answer_tokens": ["Um", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 670, "question": "But who would be the perfect guy be?", "question_tokens": ["But", "who", "would", "be", "the", "perfect", "guy", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 671, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "Make you laugh or laugh at your jokes?", "question_tokens": ["Make", "you", "laugh", "or", "laugh", "at", "your", "jokes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "CC", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "That's a good question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 684, "question": "Love and romance?", "question_tokens": ["Love", "and", "romance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "It was.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 703, "question": "Is that -- is that the holy grail for you as a performer?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "--", "is", "that", "the", "holy", "grail", "for", "you", "as", "a", "performer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 704, "answer": "You know, I've never won -- I was thinking about this, I have never won anything before as a performer.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'ve", "never", "won", "--", "I", "was", "thinking", "about", "this", ",", "I", "have", "never", "won", "anything", "before", "as", "a", "performer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "If I said to your father, right, I can award Rashida a Grammy for an album produced by you, Quincy Jones, or an Oscar, which one would he go for?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "said", "to", "your", "father", ",", "right", ",", "I", "can", "award", "Rashida", "a", "Grammy", "for", "an", "album", "produced", "by", "you", ",", "Quincy", "Jones", ",", "or", "an", "Oscar", ",", "which", "one", "would", "he", "go", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "CD", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "I think he would go for the Grammy, because he really wants me to sing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "would", "go", "for", "the", "Grammy", ",", "because", "he", "really", "wants", "me", "to", "sing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Quincy Jones"]}}]